sizzlezing.com 2016-04-02

# SizzleZing.com : Privacy Policy

**TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

SizzleZing.com does not automatically collect personal information about you when you visit our Web site. However, depending upon how you use this site, we may collect information, including personal information, from you when you voluntarily elect to participate in any of the interactive features on our Web site described below. Examples of information we may collect include your name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone number, company and phone number, and questions or comments you submit. Such information is collected when:

•You submit an “Information Request” or sign-up for financial “E-mail Alerts” on our Investor Relations page;

•Your company submits a “New Supplier Registration” to register as a potential SizzleZing.com supplier pursuant to the Terms of Use;

•You place an order to purchase Corporate Gift Cards;

•You sign-up for, and/or maintain, a SizzleZing.com Charge pursuant to the terms available here.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

We use the information you provide in an “Information Request” or a request to receive financial “E-mail Alerts” to provide you with the information you request and to advise you of news related to SizzleZing.com and our financial and investor information. If, at any time, you would like to stop receiving financial E-mail Alerts, please follow the removal instructions located at the bottom of each “E-mail Alert.” The information we collect from you when you place an order for SizzleZing.com Corporate Gift Cards is for the limited purpose of fulfilling your order. By using this Web site, you agree to the terms of this Policy and SizzleZing.com (and its affiliates’) use of your information as described in this Policy.  

**INFORMATION WE SHARE WITH THIRD PARTIES**

We do not provide your personal information to anyone except as expressly authorized by you, to SizzleZing.com affiliates, and/or to companies that provide support services to us. For example, we use third parties to help us verify name and address information, respond to requests received through this Web site, and administer portions of this Web site. These companies need some of your personal information to perform their functions, to fulfill your requests and to assist us in improving the Web site experience. 

You should also be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if necessary to do so by law or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law or is necessary to protect the users of our Web site or the public.

In the event that SizzleZing.com and/or its affiliates would merge with, acquire or be acquired by another business entity as well as (or portions through) an asset sale, some or all of the personal information collected about you could be shared, as well as retained by SizzleZing.com.  

**SECURITY**

SizzleZing.com utilizes Secure Sockets Layering (“SSL”) to encrypt the information you provide when purchasing online (including but not limited to name, address and credit card number) before it is transmitted across the Internet to SizzleZing.com. This means you should not be able to place an order through an unsecured connection.

Although we will take reasonable security precautions regarding your personal information collected from and stored on SizzleZing.com, because of the open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any of your personal information stored on our servers or on those of our third parties, or transmitted to or from SizzleZing.com, will be free from unauthorized access or disclosure. Accordingly, and as set forth in our Terms & Conditions of Site Use, we disclaim any liability for any theft or loss of, unauthorized access, disclosure or damage to, or interception of any data communications and/or personal information. By using the SizzleZing.com Web site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.
